speedypc.com 2018-12-23

# SpeedyPC – Legal - Privacy Policy

SpeedyPC SOFTWARE is dedicated to maintaining the confidentiality of your personal information, and ensuring that it remains secure and protected at all times. This document explains our Privacy Policy, and how the information you transfer to SpeedyPC SOFTWARE is utilized.

## How we collect information

We collect information from you including name, address, email address, etc. when you purchase or register SpeedyPC Software programs and when you download a evaluation version. This information is used to verify transactions during use of SpeedyPC Software programs or the SpeedyPC Software website. Payment processing merchants utilized by SpeedyPC Software and SpeedyPC Software customers use the same careful privacy criteria as SpeedyPC Software. The SpeedyPC Software website is not intended for users under the age of 18, and SpeedyPC Software does not intentionally gather information on users under the age of 18.

To unsubscribe from future communications, click here. 

SpeedyPC Software is not responsible for the information posted by users on public message boards, blogs, forums, etc., nor does SpeedyPC Software supervise the potential use of this information by third-parties. SpeedyPC Software makes no claims of privacy or confidentiality for items which users post in public spaces.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To improve customer service**  
(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
  * **To process and confirm transactions**  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To contact you to confirm information provided
  * To complete your customer registration
  * To allow us to provide personalized content created around preferences, ideas, and suggestions provided
  * To allow us to give early warnings for the termination of evaluation periods, or the continuation of evaluation periods, or early warnings for the termination of software licenses, or the continuation of software licenses.

SpeedyPC Software may release personal information at times when it is necessary to enforce our End User Licensing Agreement, Terms of Use, or other agreements (i.e.: to defend our intellectual property rights). These agreements can be found on the SpeedyPC Software website and the End User Licensing Agreement can also be found within the software. SpeedyPC Software may release or utilize your personal information when required by law, or when SpeedyPC Software ascertains that relevant statutes and laws would require this release.”

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.

## Are external links provided?

Yes, SpeedyPC Software may choose to include links to third-party websites. These websites may be related to SpeedyPC Software and its partners, or may be unassociated websites but considered relevant. Any websites which SpeedyPC Software links to are not covered by this Privacy Statement, and SpeedyPC Software makes no claims or guarantees to the Privacy Statement, Terms, Conditions, etc. of external sites. Review each site's Privacy Policy for details on their own policies.

## Cookie Policy

**What Are Cookies?**

We define a cookie as any string of data and information that is automatically stored on your computer upon access to our websites.

**Browser Cookies**

SpeedyPC Software employs cookies to assign temporary identification numbers to machines that access our services. This information enables us to deliver faster service capabilities to our customers or to our affiliates and/or other sales partners, prevent denial of service attacks on our systems, detect and prevent fraudulent transactions, and assist with awarding proper sales credit to ourselves or our partners.  
SpeedyPC Software cookies are 1) of limited duration, 2) less than 5KB in length, 3) only visible to SpeedyPC Software, and 4) devoid of any personally identifiable information. You can learn more about cookies by visiting websites such as <http://www.allaboutcookies.org/> You can set your web browser to warn you when cookies are sent. You can also choose not to have cookies sent at all. Both of these can be done through your browser settings. Turning off cookies may prevent you access to website features and may cause some of our services to not function as intended.

**Flash Cookies**

Shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, may be used to remember your preferences or personalize content based on what you view on our website. Advertisers and third parties may use Flash cookies to collect and store information. Among the differences between Flash cookies and browser cookies are the amount and type of data as well as how it is stored. You cannot remove Flash cookies by using regular browser tools. Disabling Flash cookies may prevent you from accessing some website features and some of our website features might not function properly.

**Cookie Categories**

There are different categories of cookies. The below descriptions can help you decide if and how want to use our websites.

**Essential Cookies**

This type of cookie is essential to you navigating the website and using specific features. Without these, services such as shopping carts on some sites, for example, cannot work.

**Performance Cookies**

Performance cookies are used to collect information for website improvement or for other statistic gathering activities. They are used to aggregate anonymous information about how people use our websites. For example, performance cookies are used to collect information about such things as which pages are most often viewed and if you receive error messages. This information is used to fix issues and to personalize your website viewing experience so that you are shown content you have indicated you might enjoy. Third-party advertisers may be allowed to put performance cookies on your device via ads on our websites. These third-party cookies collect information to determine which ads to show, how often to show certain ads, and in which locations on websites the ads are most successful. It is easy to manage or delete performance cookies. Below there are links to easy-to-follow instructions on how to do this.

**Functionality Cookies**

We, or service providers acting on our behalf, may put functionality cookies onto your device. These cookies are used to remember your settings and preferences and to provide enhanced features you have selected. These cookies collect anonymous information. If you have an account with us and are logged in, the information collected by these cookies may be associated with your account. We do not collect browsing behavior information from websites that we do not operate. We never share with third parties or advertisers the information collected by functionality cookies. There may be times where we allow third parties to provide you with content, experiences, or services. In these situations, the third party may place a functionality cookie on your device. Their functionality cookies work the same way as ours.  
If you choose to delete functionality cookies, any settings you picked will not be retained.

**Advertising Cookies**

If you see ads with an “i” symbol, you can click it to learn more about behavioral targeting advertising. You can also find out additional information at www.youronlinechoices.eu

**Third-Party Targeted Advertising Cookies**

These cookies may be put onto your device by ad networks, data exchanges, third-party advertisers, service providers, or marketing analytics. These cookies collect information about your browsing activities from multiple websites. This information is used display relevant ads on our websites. These cookies may also measure the effectiveness of advertising campaigns. The information collected by these cookies does not identify you personally. We can request that third-party advertising providers turn off their advertising cookies.

**SpeedyPC Software Targeted Advertising Cookies**

We may place targeted advertising cookies on your device (or a service provider may do it on our behalf). We may use these cookies on our websites and in tandem with our content and ads on third-party websites to try to show you relevant ads. These cookies may also be used to limit the number of times the same ad is displayed. These cookies collect anonymous information. If you have a registered account with us, the information collected may be associated with your account.  
We or the third party setting the cookie is responsible for obtaining your consent.

**Registered Users**

If you are a registered user, we may use cookies and other tracking technology to analyze your use of our websites. If you have opted in to receiving emails from us, we may use cookies to customize future messages to ensure they are relevant to you. We may use cookies in email messages to see, for example, if they have been opened or which links you clicked. This allows us to customize future content to your interests. We do not share your contact information with third parties unless you have given us explicit permission.

**How to Disable Cookies through Your Browser**

In your web browser, you can choose to accept or decline cookies. You can also set your browser to ask you before it accepts cookies from websites you visit. If you decline cookies, you may not have access to all of the features available on our websites. If you use different computers, you need to ensure that each browser is set to your preferences. Any cookies that have been installed in the cookie folder of your web browser can be deleted. Below are links to specific instructions for popular web browsers:  
**Windows Explorer:** <http://windows.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-vista/block-or-allow-cookies>  
**Microsoft Edge:** <https://privacy.microsoft.com/en-us/windows-10-microsoft-edge-and-privacy>  
**Google Chrome:** [https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en&p=cpn_cookies)  
**Mozilla Firefox:** [https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)  
**Apple Safari:** [https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?viewlocale=en_US&locale=en_US)

**Delete Flash Cookies**

Use this link to delete and disable flash cookies: <http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager02.html#118539>

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

## Children's Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions documentation establishing the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of our website.

## Your Consent

By using the SpeedyPC Software site or the SpeedyPC Software program you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If our privacy policy is changed, this page will be accordingly updated and altered.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact SpeedyPC Software through our Support section.
